Hello friends, my name is Vijay Shankar
Singh and I regularly
bring videos related to the stock market, so
whoever needs any information regarding stock market investment etc. should
subscribe to our channel. So the
topic I want to discuss with you
friends is
Idea First Bank.
As I tell you friends, Idea
First Bank is a bank with a lot of potential
and a multibagger
stock of the future. We buy this stock from
here. Friends, if we
fold it for 10 years or 12 years through Vimana, then even otherwise its
shares would not have remained below Rs 500 and Rs 1000. It also has a
very important role. The bank is continuously
expanding its branches.
This business is continuously starting. Right now,
friends, it is available for around Rs 19-20. It is
possible that you can come from here and go
down to the book level of Rs 15.
But we have taken
our position in this bank.
Recently, friends, the result of Leadership First One
came, that result has surprised everyone. It has been a
very positive result which was the March
quarter. Jio has made a net profit,
meaning a  78.15 crores whereas
in the same quarter last year the
loss was on 21.8 crores so you can imagine
how big a change it is and this was to be discussed so the
banks have a very
big
quality or should we say their brain,
their net interest margin is NRHM
that we give money to banks, when
we give money to the bank then the
bank provides us
that money is used by the bank in its business, when it is taken then
they also
get some interest on that loan as everyone knows so there is a
tight margin, whatever they give us, they get it
from the loan, whether it is the new
interest margin or
Pushkar net interest margin has also increased
friends it has increased by 40 percent
it means that if seen in comparison to the previous month then
in this March it is 40 percent bigger
and after becoming friends it has become 1563 crores which is
very important if we talk about this margin then
which was 3.0 last year it has increased to 1563 crores this year  It is
4.24, I am
going to go, the second question means it is a good
group
and if you see friends, the
good things about it is that
its NDA which is like and very good,
which is the entry of how much default happens in the various
types of loans provided by the banks, then
its index which
was 2.83 in the last quarter of last year has come down to
2.6 percent, that is, it has benefited here also, there has been
improvement here also, so if you see
friends, it is continuously improving by one and a half, it is getting
better, and if we talk about net NPA, then
net NPA which is
below 4 percent, which was earlier
3.23 percent, is Hindu, there is a
gross NPA, it is fragmented, so by 2030 let's
talk about more attempts, friends, then it has been cut from 1.3 percent to
point note 4%, so this is the thing,
friends, there are many things about it which we
hope for.  The meaning of the current
account and SIM account is that the banks get the
maximum benefit, it is a huge
benefit because the rate of
interest on the bank account is low, there is some power in it, so for
how many days the money will remain in it, then
you will be entitled to the interest, because
all the banks focus more on the account, so
its development today is good, it is big
and for this we talk about the figures,
friends, on this account the
CMD of this account, Mr.
Vaidyanath has given him a lot of satisfaction
and he has told friends that the
4658 crores that have come this time, that it will be increased in
future and the memories are
still remembered, friends, Vaidyanath is a
big entrepreneur in himself and
this kind of person, at one time he had made
ICICI Bank the
largest retail banking,
after this when he came out of SSC Bank,
he had
established a company named Capital First which was a
microfinance company and like
Bajaj Finance's business, he had established a company parallel to it, due to
Indore
APL rules and fund requirements,
he had established his own company  This bank was
merged with IDFC Bank, after which its name became
IDFC Bank.
So, IDBI First Night friends, it has
an excellent business and excellent
management, but as per the religious discourse,
in the coming 10-12 years, friends, it will
become a very big bank, there will be a big
twist in this bank, the idea first
match is that
friends, you should include IDFC First Bank
in your portfolio in every way
and efforts should be made, which should be kept increasing, the more it goes
down, the more it increases, the more it increases, right now its
market capital is quite low, if we
talk about marketability then friends, it is
clearly below and in comparison to this, if you
look at other big banks, so look at this bank,
Axis Bank and one, this Jersey
West is above 5 lakh crores, if you look at Axis Bank, it is
above 3 lakh crores, so
sooner or later, the way it has an
aggressive policy, friends,
its market will also reach lakhs of crores and so when the
market goes up, there will be circulation of things like Twitter, so
this will be the point, it should be kept under watch
and long turning point, so
in any case, this stock should be kept in the portfolio,
IDFC First
I will discuss another staff in the bank,
friends, that is the topic
that I keep talking to you about again and again, that
is demand.
Friends, in
EMA Super Mart, the
company has seen results of this too in the
recent past and amidst the corona virus pandemic,
where the business of all the companies is
declining, there is some problem,
so it is due to demand and
others, you will see that the revenue, friends, is
24 percent bigger and talking about profit,
friends, it has increased by 42%, friends, he is the
head of divorce related astrology,
friends, he is just a millionaire and the
money he has made is completely through
stock markets,
analyzing companies is his old
work, hence what should be the goodness in the said company, that is the
science, based on that,
he has
given all those goodness in his mind, the business model of the mind,
friends, is a very unique business
model, this company has opened its Play Store, by
showing off its glitz and glamour, it
reduces the trust of the
customers, it gives it to minimum people,
it gets more margin,
companies get to keep their products in its store  It remains
eager because the
money of the companies' products is returned very
quickly. If we compare them with the market of other companies, then if we
talk about the market, then it is the
growth of Pabla ji's constipation towards the middle of the technology of Kutch. Even when it comes to the store
of the market, the payment to Parle ji is done in
about 7 days,
their payment is done hardly in 15 days
and their inventory is there only after the new year
and ends, their entry is believed to be
finished within 10 days, it is
not a deft company, please the shares are
very less
and he is a very dynamic person, businessman,
get business, I have a very good
management, its stock, the company is very
strong, so friends, tomatoes should also be
kept in vote banks under all circumstances, many times
in this video I keep discussing the demand,
if you talk about March 2020,
friends, then the revenue has been 6255 crores
and if we look at the previous year now, then it has been
5061 crores, that is, there is
23.6 percent increase in it and  If you
want to see, then the Twitter margin which has
fallen, the negative news nutrition, it has come down a bit by
6.7 percent, that will
go away and if you see, the net profit margin, which was
308 percent last year, has also increased this year, so
see, friend, the company is continuously growing
and in the results of 20, you
can do very well about Halt, I am
not able to decide the result of the balance sheet,
but the overall result has been seen,
friends, Bhimart is a continuously growing
company and here too, in the coming
time, there will be a very big multibagger stock,
its IPL was of ₹300 in 2017,
friends, it was listed at ₹600, now it is doing
great at ₹24, that is, it has
increased eight times, the
market capital of Goods Health Kuru is
that keep putting in the upcoming changes in Nifty,
friends,
in the month of September
and the company is a big contender to be included in Nifty,
but the problem is that it is
not there in A friend right now
and  Friends, there are many such clay companies
whose market capital is Sikkim.
Yunus has already acquired a bigger company than this
and has been included in the top 11 market list of the country in terms of capital.
Friends, the topic is
half over,
very soon it will go into the top ten, it is
coming very soon, so
this is a very big stock of Nifty, it should be
kept in the reserves, friends, it should be remembered for a long time. So
friends, this is all for today, whoever
you are, you can ask any questions. Jai
Hind, Jai Bharat.